Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- A Large Family (Akbal el bakari), 1949; ref38; Omara, Ibrahim
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Mahmoud El Meleigy, Abdel Meguid Choukry, Taheyya Kariokka, 1949; ref38_000002; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Fez/Tarboush; Men; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Lanterns/Lamps; Costumes; Women; Actors; Films; Negative Images; Hats
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari), 1949; ref38_000003; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Women; Costumes; Films; Belly Dancers; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Hats; Chandeliers; Negative Images; Actors; Dancing; Belly Dancers
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, Abdel Meguid Choukry, Mahmoud El Meleigy, Taheyya Kariokka, 1949; ref38_000004; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Arabic Writing; Fur Garments; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Hats
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1949; ref38_000005; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Head Covers/Veils; Swords/Knives; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Costumes; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Women; Men; Weapons
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1949; ref38_000006; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Clocks/Watches; Head Covers/Veils; Paintings; Jewelry; Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Furnishings
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Mahmoud El Meleigy, Ismail Yasin, 1949; ref38_000007; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Negative Images; Costumes; Films; Actors; Furnishings
  - A Large Family (Akbal el bakari) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1949; ref38_000008; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 36)
- People's Gossip, 1949; ref39
  - People's Gossip | Actors in Image: Said Suleiman, Ibrahim Hamouda, Hassan Kamel, 1949; ref39_000001; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Facial Hair; Negative Images; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Hats; Costumes; Films; Actors; Men
  - People's Gossip | Actors in Image: Shadya, 1949; ref39_000002; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Mirrors
  - People's Gossip | Actors in Image: Shadya, Ibrahim Hamouda, Mohsen Hassanein, 1949; ref39_000003; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Facial Hair; Jewelry; Fez/Tarboush; Head Covers/Veils; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Women; Radios; Hats
  - People's Gossip | Actors in Image: Zuzu Muhammed, Ibrahim Hamouda, 1949; ref39_000004; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Women; Men; Negative Images; Facial Hair; Costumes; Actors; Films; Furnishings
- The Princess's Secret, 1949; ref40; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Princess's Secret | Actors in Image: Hassan Fayek, Koka, Kamal El Shennawy, 1949; ref40_000001; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Cars/Trucks; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Jewelry; Fez/Tarboush; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men; Transportation; Hats
- Days of My Youth, 1950; ref41
  - Days of My Youth | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, 1950; ref41_000001; Madkour, Gamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Fez/Tarboush; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Women; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Hats
  - Days of My Youth | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, 1950; ref41_000002; Madkour, Gamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Men; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Hats
  - Days of My Youth | Actors in Image: Aziza Helmy, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1950; ref41_000003; Madkour, Gamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 42)
    Women; Jewelry; Carriages/Coaches; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men
  - Days of My Youth | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Kamal El Shennawy, 1950; ref41_000004; Madkour, Gamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Facial Hair; Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Clocks/Watches; Lanterns/Lamps
  - Days of My Youth | Actors in Image: Ahmed Allam, Kamal El Shennawy, 1950; ref41_000005; Madkour, Gamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Fez/Tarboush; Cigarettes; Hats; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Actors; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Oh, Men, 1950; ref42; Rafla, Helmy
  - Oh, Men | Actors in Image: Mohamed Fawzy, 1950; ref42_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Chandeliers; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Furnishings
  - Oh, Men | Actors in Image: Madiha Yousri, Mohamed Fawzy, Zinat Sedki, 1950; ref42_000003; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Jewelry; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings
  - Oh, Men | Actors in Image: Mohamed Kamal Elmasry, Mohamed Fawzy, 1950; ref42_000004; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Costumes; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Hats
- Just My Luck!, 1950; ref43; Barakat, Henry
  - Just My Luck! | Actors in Image: Serag Mounir, Zaki Rostom | Car in Image: 1949 Lincoln Cosmopolitan Sedan, 1950; ref43_000001; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Cars/Trucks; Turbans; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Doors/Entrances; Transportation; Hats
  - Just My Luck! | Actors in Image: Abdelmonem Ismail, Stephan Rosty, Salah Mansour, Serag Mounir, Karem Mahmoud, Mohammed Attia, 1950; ref43_000002; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Fez/Tarboush; Men; Costumes; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Hats
  - Just My Luck! | Actors in Image: Salah Mansour, Serag Mounir, Mohammed Attia, Zaki Rostom, 1950; ref43_000003; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Clocks/Watches; Costumes; Hats
  - Just My Luck! | Actors in Image: Zaki Rostom, Mimi Shakib, Shadya, Wedad Hamdy, 1950; ref43_000004; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Fez/Tarboush; Negative Images; Films; Boys; Jewelry; Costumes; Facial Hair; Men; Women; Actors; Furnishings; Children; Hats
  - Just My Luck! | Actors in Image: Wedad Hamdy, Mimi Shakib, Shadya, 1950; ref43_000005; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Food; Head Covers/Veils; Boys; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Actors; Women; Food; Children
- The Girl From Paris, 1950; ref44; Rafla, Helmy
  - The Girl From Paris | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Mohamed Fawzy, 1950; ref44_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Costumes; Lanterns/Lamps; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Women; Men
  - The Girl From Paris | Actors in Image: Laila Fawzy, 1950; ref44_000002; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Lanterns/Lamps; Women; Negative Images; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Films; Drinks/Beverages; Bags/Purses; Jewelry; Actors; Men; Costumes
  - The Girl From Paris | Actors in Image: Aziz Othman, Mohamed Fawzy, 1950; ref44_000003; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Costumes; Films; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Negative Images; Actors; Mirrors; Lanterns/Lamps; Furnishings
  - The Girl From Paris | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, 1950; ref44_000004; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Drinks/Beverages; Telephones; Men; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - The Girl From Paris | Actors in Image: Mohamed Fawzy, Aziz Othman, 1950; ref44_000005; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Lanterns/Lamps
- The Marriage Bureau, 1950; ref45
  - The Marriage Bureau | Actors in Image: Houda Shams El Den, Mohamed Amin, 1950; ref45_000001; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings
  - The Marriage Bureau | Actors in Image: Soad Mekawy, 1950; ref45_000002; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Girls; Jewelry; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - The Marriage Bureau | Actors in Image: Fouad Shafik, Mohamed Amin, 1950; ref45_000003; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Arabic Writing; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Fez/Tarboush; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Hats
  - The Marriage Bureau | Actors in Image: Houda Shams El Den, 1950; ref45_000004; Helmy, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Fez/Tarboush; Drinks/Beverages; Lanterns/Lamps; Facial Hair; Men; Hats
- The Millionaire, 1950; ref46; Rafla, Helmy
  - The Millionaire | Actors in Image: Camellia, Ismail Yasin, 1950; ref46_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Custodial History
    98 x 149 cm
    Musical Instruments; Fez/Tarboush; Costumes; Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Women
  - The Millionaire | Actors in Image: Camellia, 1950; ref46_000002; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Women; Negative Images; Actors; Films; Costumes; Individual Portraits
- The Much Loved One, 1950; ref47
  - The Much Loved One | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, Ragaa Abdo, 1950; ref47_000001; Attia, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 149 cm (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Facial Hair; Films; Negative Images; Men; Women; Costumes; Actors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings
  - The Much Loved One | Actors in Image: Ragaa Abdo, Ismail Yasin, 1950; ref47_000002; Attia, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 149 cm (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Costumes; Negative Images; Arabic Writing; Films; Men; Women; Actors
  - The Much Loved One | Actors in Image: Samir Ezzat, Magda, 1950; ref47_000003; Attia, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 149 cm (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Women; Furnishings
- You and Me, 1950; ref48; Badr Khan, Ahmed
  - You and Me | Actors in Image: Hagar Hamdy, Ismail Yasin, 1950; ref48_000001; Badr Khan, Ahmed; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Jewelry; Kissing; Costumes; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Women; Men
  - You and Me | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, Mohamed El Kahlawy, Hassan Fayek, Hagar Hamdy, Mohamed Kamal Elmasry, Zinat Sedki, 1950; ref48_000002; Badr Khan, Ahmed; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Fez/Tarboush; Negative Images; Films; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Telephones; Weapons; Clocks/Watches; Actors; Men; Women; Costumes; Hats; Furnishings
  - You and Me | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, 1950; ref48_000003; Badr Khan, Ahmed; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Telephones; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Men; Costumes; Musical Instruments
- Fayek and Rayeq, 1951; ref49; Rafla, Helmy
  - Fayek and Rayeq | Actors in Image: Abdel-Wareth Asar, Ismail Yasin, Nagwa Salem, 1951; ref49_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Costumes; Negative Images; Actors; Films; Men; Women; Hats
  - Fayek and Rayeq | Actors in Image: Karem Mahmoud, Taheyya Kariokka, Ismail Yasin, 1951; ref49_000002; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Kissing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Costumes; Jewelry; Clocks/Watches; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Furnishings
  - Fayek and Rayeq | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, 1951; ref49_000003; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Prayer Beads; Outdoors; Hats; Spears; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
- Good News!, 1951; ref50; Kamel, Abbas
  - Good News! | Actors in Image: Karem Mahmoud, Laila Fawzy, 1951; ref50_000001; Kamel, Abbas; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Cars/Trucks; Fez/Tarboush; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Women; Transportation; Hats
  - Good News! | Actors in Image: Laila Fawzy, Karem Mahmoud, 1951; ref50_000002; Kamel, Abbas; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Men; Women; Gloves; Clocks/Watches; Books; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Good News! | Actors in Image: Elsayed Bedir, Hagar Hamdy, Karem Mahmoud, 1951; ref50_000003; Kamel, Abbas; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Men; Women; Belly Dancers; Oud; Head Covers/Veils; Turbans; Hats; Jewelry; Musical Instruments; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
- Street Children, 1951; ref52; Wahby, Youssef
  - Street Children | Actors in Image: Zaki Rostom, Aziza Helmy, Abdelmonem Basiony, Madiha Yousri, Zouzou Shakib, 1951; ref52_000001; Wahby, Youssef; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Fez/Tarboush; Clocks/Watches; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Men; Women; Jewelry; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Hats
  - Street Children | Actors in Image: Kamal Hussain, Abdelmonem Basiony, 1951; ref52_000002; Wahby, Youssef; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Boys; Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Children; Hats
- The Missing Link/Alhalqh Elmafqodh, 1948; ref53; Lama, Ibrahim
  - The Missing Link/Alhalqh Elmafqodh | Actors in Image: Faten Hamama, Samir Abdullah Lama, 1948; ref53_000001; Lama, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Typewriters; Arabic Writing; Clocks/Watches; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Costumes; Furnishings
- As You Like, 1952; ref55; Rafla, Helmy
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Laila Fawzy, Mohsen Sarhan, Taheyya Kariokka, Abdelhamid Zaki, Ismail Yasin, 1952; ref55_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Turbans; Hats; Children; Fez/Tarboush; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Costumes; Actors; Women
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Mohsen Sarhan, Ismail Yasin, 1952; ref55_000002; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Telephones; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Actors; Furnishings
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, Wedad Hamdy, Mohsen Sarhan, 1952; ref55_000003; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Jewelry; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Costumes
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, 1952; ref55_000004; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Children; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Furnishings
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Laila Fawzy, Mohsen Sarhan, Taheyya Kariokka, Aziz Othman, 1952; ref55_000005; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Weddings; Fez/Tarboush; Jewelry; Belly Dancers; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Women; Gloves; Tuxedos; Hats
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Mohsen Sarhan, Taheyya Kariokka, Ismail Yasin, 1952; ref55_000006; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Drinks/Beverages; Lanterns/Lamps; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Women; Men
  - As You Like | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, Mohsen Sarhan, 1952; ref55_000007; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Jewelry; Men; Women; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Head Covers/Veils
- Amaal, 1952; ref56; Youssef Malouf
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000001; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000002; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000003; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000004; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000005; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000006; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000007; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000008; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000009; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000010; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000011; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000012; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000013; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000014; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000015; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000016; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000017; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000018; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000019; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000020; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000021; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000022; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000023; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000024; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Amaal, 1952; ref56_000025; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 25)
- My Beloved, 1952; ref57; 4794; Rafla, Helmy
  - My Beloved, 1952; ref57_000001; 4795; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 80 x 120 cm (Box 7, Folder 26)
- The Wedding Photo, 1952; ref60; Amir, Hassan
  - The Wedding Photo | Actors in Image: Fayrouz, Zahrat Al Oula, 1952; ref60_000001; Amir, Hassan; 1 negatives (Box 7, Folder 35)
    File Plan
    Women; Girls; Costumes; Jewelry; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Furnishings
- Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik), 1953; ref62; Hassan Reda
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Mohamed Amin, Kamal El Shennawy, 1953; ref62_000001; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 41)
    Facial Hair; Hats; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, 1953; ref62_000002; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Women; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, 1953; ref62_000003; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Facial Hair; Men; Drinks/Beverages; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Furnishings
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Abd El Ghany El Sayed, 1953; ref62_000004; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Men; Violins; Musical Instruments; Microphones; Facial Hair; Outdoors; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Zinat Sedki, 1953; ref62_000005; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Fez/Tarboush; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Costumes; Actors; Hats
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, Mohamed El Deeb, 1953; ref62_000006; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 46)
    Turbans; Drinks/Beverages; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Actors; Films; Men; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Mohammed al-Tabi, 1953; ref62_000007; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 47)
    Boys; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Men; Actors; Costumes; Children; Drinks/Beverages
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Houda Shams El Den, Kamal El Shennawy, Mohamed El Deeb, 1953; ref62_000008; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 48)
    Facial Hair; Gloves; Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Omar El Gizawy, Kamal El Shennawy, 1953; ref62_000009; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 49)
    Men; Facial Hair; Newspapers/Magazines; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Mohamed Amin, Kamal El Shennawy, Houda Shams El Den, 1953; ref62_000010; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 50)
    Fez/Tarboush; Costumes; Facial Hair; Bags/Purses; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Women; Hats
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Houda Shams El Den, Kamal El Shennawy, 1953; ref62_000011; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 51)
    Men; Women; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Between Us (Baynaa wa baynik) | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, Houda Shams El Den, Mohamed Amin, 1953; ref62_000012; Hassan Reda; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Cameras; Facial Hair; Costumes; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
- Gilded Youth, 1953; ref63; Saifi, Hassan
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in image: Katie, Mimi Shakib, Nagah Salem, 1953; ref63_000001; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 54)
    Bags/Purses; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, Nagah Salem, 1953; ref63_000002; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 55)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men; Jewelry
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Mimi Shakib, Katie, Nagah Salem, 1953; ref63_000003; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Bags/Purses; Clocks/Watches; Flower Garlands/Bouquets
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, 1953; ref63_000004; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 57)
    Women; Negative Images; Mirrors; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Costumes; Jewelry; Actors; Films; Clocks/Watches
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Mimi Shakib, Nagah Salem, Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, 1953; ref63_000005; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 58)
    Facial Hair; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Hats; Bags/Purses; Telephones; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Men; Costumes; Furnishings
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, Katie, Ismail Yasiin, 1953; ref63_000006; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 59)
    Jewelry; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Women; Men
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Nagah Salem, 1953; ref63_000007; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 7, Folder 60)
    Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Bags/Purses; Head Covers/Veils; Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Costumes; Men
  - Gilded Youth | Actors in Image: Serag Mounir, Mimi Shakib, 1953; ref63_000008; Saifi, Hassan; 1 negatives; 94 x 129 cm (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Facial Hair; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Women
- The Night Train, 1953; ref64; Zulfiquar, Ezzeddine
  - The Night Train | Actors in Image: Reyad El Kasabgy, 1953; ref64_000001; Zulfiquar, Ezzeddine; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Guns; Negative Images; Films; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Prayer Beads; Turbans; Hats; Weapons; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Arabic Writing; Costumes